Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings
  - Video 881: (Chinese), CCTV labeled, "A-20", cuid2144 (Box 141)
  - Video 882: Thunder Storm (I, II), CCTV labeled "A25", cuid2145 (Box 141)
  - Video 883: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "048", cuid2146 (Box 141)
  - Video 884: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "232" "AAFF 5/12", cuid2147 (Box 141)
  - Video 885: "Interview: Taka, Al Wong," CCTV labeled "233", cuid2148 (Box 141)
  - Video 886: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "241", cuid2149 (Box 141)
  - Video 887: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "260", cuid2150 (Box 141)
  - Video 888: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "274", cuid2151 (Box 141)
  - Video 889: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "275", cuid2152 (Box 141)
  - Video 890: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "294, cuid2153 (Box 141)
  - Video 891: Unidentified, cuid2154 (Box 141)
  - Video 892: Unidentified, cuid2155 (Box 141)
  - Video 893: Asian Americans in the Performing Arts, Demo @ Bijou Theatre, 5/16/74, "Ride the WindsOut of Town", cuid2156 (Box 141)
  - Video 894: CCTV May 27, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid2157 (Box 142)
  - Video 895: CCTV December 13, 1982 Broadcast tape: News (ILWGU 23-25), cuid2158 (Box 142, Box Shared Tamiment 111)
  - Video 896: CCTV December 14, 1982 Broadcast tape: News (Chan is Missing), cuid2159 (Box 142)
  - Video 897: CCTV December 16, 1982 Broadcast tape: News, cuid2160 (Box 142)
  - Video 898: CCTV April 23, 1982 Broadcast tape, cuid2161 (Box 142)
  - Video 899: CCTV February 14, 1982 Broadcast tape: News, Housing in Chinatown Henry Street 54-56, Madison Street 109 (1980), Roman Tam Special, cuid2162 (Box 142)
  - Video 900: Chinatown: 1984 (Work in Progress) by Nancy Tong, 4 minutes 32 seconds, April 5, 1984, cuid2163 (Box 142)
  - Video 901: Disarmament Special, 30 minutes, June 9, 1982, cuid2164 (Box 142)
  - Video 902: CCTV News Special, Kwok Gallery, Chinese Painter Wang Da Wen, Paper Angels, Street Vendors in Chinatown, cuid2165 (Box 142)
  - Video 903: Henry Street Tenant Strike, producer: Peter Chow, cuid2166 (Box 142)
  - Video 904: Tracking On, March 30, 1988, CCTV labeled "1147", cuid2167 (Box 143)
  - Video 905: Tracking On, April 6, 1988, CCTV labeled "1199", cuid2168 (Box 143)
  - Video 906: Tracking On, April 13, 1988, CCTV labeled "1156", cuid2169 (Box 143)
  - Video 907: Tracking On, April 20, 1988, CCTV labeled "1164", cuid2170 (Box 143)
  - Video 908: Tracking On, April 27, 1988, "How to Become a Fascinating Speaker" directed by Fu-Ding Cheng, "3 Wishes" directed by Art Nomura, CCTV labeled "1169", cuid2171 (Box 143)
  - Video 909: Tracking On, May 5, 1988, cuid2172 (Box 143)
  - Video 910: Tracking On, May 8, 1988, CCTV labeled "1184", cuid2173 (Box 143)
  - Video 911: Tracking On, May 18, 1988, "My Prison" directed by Hiroya Sakurai, "In Plus/Pulse" directed by Norie Sato, "Aviary Species in Soda Soup" directed by Tomiyo Sasaki, CCTV labeled "1203", cuid2174 (Box 143)
  - Video 912: Biological Cycle, My Life, Horizon, Bunruku, by Ko Nakajima, CCTV labeled "U49", cuid2175 (Box 144)
  - Video 913: Camera Work (Demo), CCTV labeled "U91", cuid2176 (Box 144)
  - Video 914: Chan is Missing/ Wayne Wang, tape II, CCTV labeled U66, cuid2177 (Box 144)
  - Video 915: Chan Ming by Siu Kwan Chan, CCTV labeled "U69", cuid2178 (Box 144)
  - Video 916: Fung Fay Fay Special, CCTV labeled "U123", cuid2179 (Box 144)
  - Video 917: International Children's Theatre of Ghana, tape 1 of 2, CCTV labeled "U67", cuid2180 (Box 144)
  - Video 918: International Children's Theatre of Ghana, tape 2 of 2, CCTV labeled "U68", cuid2181 (Box 144)
  - Video 919: Jenny Yin Concert Part I, CCTV labeled "U121", cuid2182 (Box 144)
  - Video 920: Jenny Yin Concert Part 2, CCTV labeled "U122", cuid2183 (Box 144)
  - Video 921: Child of the Windmill by RTHK, CCTV labeled "U132", cuid2184 (Box 145)
  - Video 922: Chinese World Television Inc. AAIFF: The Only Language She Knows, The Departure, After Birth, Paraiba Woman, Ah Ying, CCTV labeled "U133", cuid2185 (Box 145)
  - Video 923: Colorful Lamp Pt. I, CCTV labeled "U126", cuid2186 (Box 145)
  - Video 924: Colorful Lamp Pt. II, CCTV labeled "U127", cuid2187 (Box 145)
  - Video 925: Fay Xiang Special Pt. 1, CCTV labeled "U124", cuid2188 (Box 145)
  - Video 926: Kenny B. Special and Fay Xiang Special Pt. 2, CCTV labeled "U125", cuid2189 (Box 145)
  - Video 927: Night of the Star, 53 min,, CCTV labeled "U117", cuid2190 (Box 145)
  - Video 928: Oh Yang Fay Fay Special Pt. 1, 60 min, CCTV labeled "U118", cuid2191 (Box 145)
  - Video 929: Run Sister Run (featuring) choreography by Cleo Parker Robinson and music by Gordon Parks, produced by Margie Soo Hoo Lee, CCTV labeled "U134", cuid2192 (Box 145)
  - Video 930: 1979 Year End Program, CCTV labeled "U27", cuid2193 (Box 146)
  - Video 931: Building Blacks (I) by Saiki Hiromu, CCTV labeled "U46", cuid2194 (Box 146)
  - Video 932: Bean Sprouts Show #1 / Children's Television Project, CCTV labeled "U12", cuid2195 (Box 146)
  - Video 933: Bean Sprouts Show #2 / Children's Television Project, CCTV labeled "U13", cuid2196 (Box 146)
  - Video 934: The Barefoot Doctor of Rural China / Diane Li, CCTV labeled "U6", cuid2197 (Box 146)
  - Video 935: The Dragon Wore Tennis Shoes by Diane Li, Raven Dance by David Kimura, 2 Performances and David Kimura, and Suzhou by Ex. Media Center U. of Call. (30 min), CCTV labeled "U8", cuid2198 (Box 146)
  - Video 936: I Quit by Hong Kong Television Broadcasting (50 min), CCTV labeled "U10", cuid2199 (Box 146)
  - Video 937: The New York Hearings (Excerpts) by Renee Tajima/ "Artists Speak" Nov. 23, 1981, 22 mins, CCTV labeled "U9", cuid2200 (Box 146)
  - Video 938: Reunion with Eng (Excerpt) by Peter Chow 1979-80, 10 mins, CCTV labeled "U7", cuid2201 (Box 146)
  - Video 939: International Women Volleyball Tournament: China vs. Japan, CCTV labeled "U24", cuid2202 (Box 147)
  - Video 940: International Women Volleyball Tournament: China vs. Japan and China vs. America, CCTV labeled "U28", cuid2203 (Box 147)
  - Video 941: International Women Volleyball Tournament: China vs. Peru, CCTV labeled "U26", cuid2204 (Box 147)
  - Video 942: Journey Through New York "Chinatown," First hour of two hours, by Tad Turner, WNYC-TV, CCTV labeled "U50", cuid2205 (Box 147)
  - Video 943: Re Dis Appearing, Mouth to Mouth, Videoeme, CCTV labeled "U51", cuid2206 (Box 147)
  - Video 944: Tea Farmer I, 10 min, CCTV labeled "U20", cuid2207 (Box 147)
  - Video 945: Tea Farmer 2, CCTV labeled "U22", cuid2208 (Box 147)
  - Video 946: Theresa Tang Special Pt. 2 (20 mins) and Oh Yang Fay Fay Special Pt. 2 (23 mins), CCTV labeled "U120", cuid2209 (Box 147)
  - Video 947: Third World Cultural perspective Tape II, Nancy Tong/Cecile Guidote, CCTV labeled "U64", cuid2210 (Box 147)
  - Video 948: Ayako and Joe by Daw-Ming Lee (39 min), CCTV labeled "U54", cuid2211 (Box 148)
  - Video 949: Becoming American The Odyssey of a Refugee Family, 60 mins, CCTV labeled "U61", cuid2212 (Box 148)
  - Video 950: Best of Vision and View Points, CCTV labeled "U88", cuid2213 (Box 148)
  - Video 951: Chan is Missing/ Wayne Wang Tape 1, 50 mins, CCTV labeled "U63", cuid2214 (Box 148)
  - Video 952: Chinese American in Mainstream Politics by Nancy Tong, CCTV labeled "U60", cuid2215 (Box 148)
  - Video 953: Dream Quest (Demo Tape), CCTV labeled "U89", cuid2216 (Box 148)
  - Video 954: Gold Mountain Dream (with English subtitle) by ACV production, Peter Chow, Wing Young, 28 mins, CCTV labeled "U14", cuid2217 (Box 148)
  - Video 955: Jesse Jackson in Chinatown Tape I by Siu Kwan Chan, 60 mins, CCTV labeled "U56", cuid2218 (Box 148)
  - Video 956: Jesse Jackson in Chinatown Tape II by Siu Kwan Chan, 60 mins, CCTV labeled "U57", cuid2219 (Box 148)
  - Video 957: Appropriate Technologists Are You Looking / Martha Stuart Communication Inc., 38 mins 38 secs, CCTV labeled "U18", cuid2220 (Box 149)
  - Video 958: Cinema: Film of the Philippines -- A Report by Tony Rayns, cuid2221 (Box 149)
  - John Ellis, Producer, Large Door Ltd. Of London, cuid2222 (Box 149)
  - Video 959: Dance and the Railroad by PBS, CCTV labeled "U4", 1984-02-24; 2018; cuid2223 (Box 149, Video cuid2223, E-records tamwag_TAM416, E-records cuid2223)
    Original Format: 3/4" Umatic, Estimated Duration: 60 min.
  - Video 960: Hong Kong Fashion Show, Governor in New York, CCTV labeled "U17", cuid2224 (Box 149)
  - Video 961: Pinoy #4/Pearls (29 min) and Vaitefe by Visual Communication (29 min), CCTV labeled "U2", cuid2225 (Box 149)
  - Video 962: A Study forA Picture is Worth a Thousand Words (1989) by Tomiyo Sasaki, cuid2226 (Box 149)
  - Video 963: Tatoo City by Emiko Omori (24 min) CCTV labeled "U15", cuid2227 (Box 149)
  - Video 964: Unfinished Business by Steven Okazaki, 60 mins,, CCTV labeled "U162/U172", cuid2228 (Box 149)
  - Video 965: Unforgettable Fire I (slide) (18 min), Unforgettable Fire II (exhibit) (13'43") by Joyce Wexler Ballard and "Contemporary Japanese Women: A Closer Look" (23'10") by Kathy Cambell and Michele Sehofield c/o Center for Media Development, U. of Massa, cuid2229 (Box 149)
  - Video 966: 1981 CCTV Workshop, Profile of Chu (??) (A Chinese Artist) (13:00 min) and Bad Dream (6:00 min), CCTV labeled "U16", cuid2230 (Box 150)
  - Video 967: 1983 Video Production Workshop Final Project by Richard Lee, cuid2231 (Box 150)
  - Video 968: 1983 Workshop -- Secrets of the Freshman and 1984 Workshop -- Shoe Repairer, CCTV labeled "UA9", cuid2232 (Box 150)
  - Video 969: 1985 Video Production Workshop, Group 3. Edit Master, cuid2233 (Box 150)
  - Video 970: 1986 Video Production Workshop, cuid2234 (Box 150)
  - Video 971: 10th Workshop, Group 2, Project 2, Master tape, cuid2235 (Box 150)
  - Video 972: Camera Training tape for Television Workshop by Asian CineVision, 19 mins, CCTV labeled "U3", cuid2236 (Box 150)
  - Video 973: Interactive Training Tape I: Camera Operation by Asian CineVision (Revised Soundtrack), 19 mins, CCTV labeled "U1", cuid2237 (Box 150)
  - Video 974: Sample of Karl Kim's Work for Workshop, cuid2238 (Box 150)
  - Video 975: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "UB83", cuid2239 (Box 151)
  - Video 976: Canadian History, English sd track, CCTV labeled "UB283", cuid2240 (Box 151)
  - Video 977: Unidentified,, CCTV labeled "UB283", cuid2241 (Box 151)
  - Video 978: Teah House (Pan Asian Production) Includes: Cocktail party (15 min), Act I (11'), Act II (11'), Act III (17' 30), CCTV labeled "UB514", cuid2242 (Box 151)
  - Video 979: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "UB516", cuid2243 (Box 151)
  - Video 980: Dance, CCTV labeled "UB543", cuid2244 (Box 151)
  - Video 981: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "UCL1", cuid2245 (Box 151)
  - Video 982: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "UCL36", cuid2246 (Box 151)
  - Video 983: Hong Kong (HK Half Mountain, HK harbor, HK junk, HK housing, HK night scene, Shanghai BK logo, Tatcher, Tatcher and Teng), CCTV labeled "UCL37", cuid2247 (Box 151)
  - Video 984: Unidentified, 1983, CCTV labeled "UD17", cuid2248 (Box 151)
  - Video 985: 1984 Workshop Group I, Proj I, Master tape, cuid2249 (Box 152)
  - Video 986: 1984 Workshop Group I, Proj I, caw(?) Master, cuid2250 (Box 152)
  - Video 987: Artists discussion, cuid2251 (Box 152)
  - Video 988: Campaign against time change, 1.33, cuid2252 (Box 152)
  - Video 989: Gunsmoke Tape, cuid2253 (Box 152)
  - Video 990: Master (Color bar/Black) (20 min), cuid2254 (Box 152)
  - Video 991: OCA Part IV (Chinese), 30 mins, cuid2255 (Box 152)
  - Video 992: Usako's Tape (Atsuko), cuid2256 (Box 152)
  - Video 993: Unidentified, cuid2257 (Box 152)
  - Video 994: 1987 Asian American International Film Festival PSA, 30 sec, cuid2258 (Box 153)
  - Video 995: 1988 Asian American International Film Festival Dubbed Trailer, #47840, cuid2259 (Box 153)
  - Video 996: Asian CineVision Graphi Opening, August 23, 1988, cuid2260 (Box 153)
  - Video 997: "ACV-AAFF" 35 mm print, 1 min, Woo Art International, cuid2261 (Box 153)
  - Video 998: ACV Opening 07/14/89, cuid2262 (Box 153)
  - Video 999: ACV Trailer 06-17-92, cuid2263 (Box 153)
  - Video 1000: "Kone" 1994, 17 mins (NTSC), Feet Unbound productions, cuid2264 (Box 153)
  - Video 1001: Videoscape '91 trailer, cuid2265 (Box 153)
  - Video 1002: Videoscape: A Preview with Chow, Hong, Audio-both, cuid2266 (Box 153)
  - Video 1003: CBS Report: Gentrification of Chinatown CBS (20 min), Bill Baird Mirronettes HBO (10 min), and American Children- Nobody's Child, 3/8/84, CCTV labeled "U36", cuid2267 (Box 154, Box Shared Tamiment 111)
  - Video 1004: East Popoo (10/3/1982), Cinema-Kuho Egal Video by Taio Tsvrumoto (4 min), CCTV labeled "U42", cuid2268 (Box 154)
  - Video 1005: Intensity by Paul Wong (B/W 1979) (23 min) and Prime Cuts by Paul Wong (1981) (20 min), CCTV labeled "U30", cuid2269 (Box 154)
  - Video 1006: Justice Overdue (King Beating, Seattle) by Rene Tajima, CCTV labeled "U34", cuid2270 (Box 154)
  - Video 1007: Monet's Garden (15 min) and Monet's Garden Super 8 by Shigeko Kubota (7'54"), CCTV labeled "U38", cuid2271 (Box 154)
  - Video 1008: Profile: Russel baba's Electric Sounds by Renee Tajima, 20 mins, CCTV labeled "U29", cuid2272 (Box 154)
  - Video 1009: Survivors by Steven Okazaki JACL, 58 mins, CCTV labeled "U35", cuid2273 (Box 154)
  - Video 1010: Third Ave by DCTV, 60 mins, CCTV labeled "U33", cuid2274 (Box 154)
  - Video 1011: Tibet by Nien-Sheng Lin PhD 1982, Lamas University Associate Professor, 46 mins, CCTV labeled "U40", cuid2275 (Box 154)
  - Video 1012: The Forest Monastery by Thamrong Prinyankit, 12 mins, CCTV labeled "U206", cuid2276 (Box 155)
  - Video 1013: Rondo by Anthony Chan, 6 mins 10 sec, CCTV labeled "U210", cuid2277 (Box 155)
  - Video 1014: Street Angel Reel I, CCTV labeled "U128", cuid2278 (Box 155)
  - Video 1015: Street Angel Reel II, CCTV labeled "U129", cuid2279 (Box 155)
  - Video 1016: Tale of the Walled City Part I by RTHK, CCTV labeled "U130", cuid2280 (Box 155)
  - Video 1017: Tale of the Walled City Part II by RTHK, CCTV labeled "U131", cuid2281 (Box 155)
  - Video 1018: Theresa Tang Special Pt. 1, 54 mins, CCTV labeled "U119", cuid2282 (Box 155)
  - Video 1019: Wise Man and the Wheel Part I and II, CCTV labeled "U44", cuid2283 (Box 155)
  - Video 1020: Women Videotape Artists: New York 1975: Shugeko Kubato by Mary Ellen Brown, 27 mins, CCTV labeled "U31", cuid2284 (Box 155)
  - Video 1021: 1982 Asian American International Video Festival films: Three Wishes by Art Nomura (10 mins), With Liberty and Justice For all by John Ishihars (17 mins 17 sec), "Birds" "Brighon" by Rii Kanzaki (9 mins), After Image Calif. 94595 by Daryl Suzu, cuid2285 (Box 156)
  - Video 1022: 1982 Asian American International Video Festival films: Cinema-Knho-Egal video, Pikkadon, After Image, Beaver Valley, Octogenesis, Superhuman Flight of Submoronic Fancies, Birds, CCTV labeled "U82", cuid2286 (Box 156)
  - Video 1023: 1983 Asian American International Video Festival films: Self Introduction I and II, It's Me Mama, Great Mother, CCTV labeled "U83", cuid2287 (Box 156)
  - Video 1024: 1983 Asian American International Video Festival films: Depot Duet, Plastic Dance, Between Day Dream and., Aminaiature Garden, Sakasa (Dud Versim), Cubist Fantasy II, Jessica Hagedorn and Ganfester Choir, CCTV labeled "U76", cuid2288 (Box 156)
  - Video 1025: 1983 Asian American International Video Festival films: Takanoko Zoku, Biological Cycle, One Edge, IN Plus / Plus, Horizan, A Study for Landscape, CCTV labeled "U77", cuid2289 (Box 156)
  - Video 1026: Allaen and Allens Coomplain (28 min) and Lake Placid 80 (4 min) by Nam Jun Paik, CCTV labeled "U78", cuid2290 (Box 156)
  - Video 1027: Chinese-Canadian History-1887 by Nancy Tong, 35 mins,, CCTV labeled "U70", cuid2291 (Box 156)
  - Video 1028: Invisible Citizen: Japanese American by Keiko Tsuno's, CCTV labeled "U75", cuid2292 (Box 156)
  - Video 1029: Monterey's Boat People by Client Nakasak / Digirolamo, CCTV labeled "U79", cuid2293 (Box 156)
  - Video 1030: 1984 Video Festival films: 1. "60 flowers, 70 capsules, 80 digits" by Arturo Cubacub (8 mins 21 sec); 2. Seascape" by Art Nomura (10 min 40 sec); 3. "Afterimage TTLS" by Norie Sato (5 mins 15 sec); 4. "Vault" by Brunce and Norman Yonemoto (12, cuid2294 (Box 157)
  - Video 1031: 1984 Video Festival films: 1. "Forbidden Rebels" by Rii Kanzaki (20 mins); 2. "Good Morning, Mr. Orwell" by Nam June Paik (35 mins), 1/28/85, CCTV labeled "U143", cuid2295 (Box 157, Box 1)
  - Video 1032: 1984 Video Festival films: 1. "Perceptions: The Vanishing Heroes" by Sandra Gin Yep and Tom Nakashima (25 mins); 2. "Perceptions: Beyond the Bomb" by Sandra Gin Yep (25 min), CCTV labeled "U147", cuid2296 (Box 157)
  - Video 1033: ABC Nightline: Mail Order Brides, CCTV labeled "U139", cuid2297 (Box 157)
  - Video 1034: Building Blocks (copy 1-A) 1980 by Hiomu Saiki, CCTV labeled "U138", cuid2298 (Box 157)
  - Video 1035: "How We Got Here: The Chinese" by Loni Ding (27 mins 30 sec) and Bean Sprouts, "Try It You'll Like It" by Children's TV Project KQED (28 mins), CCTV labeled "U145", cuid2299 (Box 157)
  - Video 1036: The Imp (Pt. II), Century Motion Picture and Distribution (International) Co. Ltd., CCTV labeled "U136", cuid2300 (Box 157)
  - Video 1037: My Memories of Old Beijing, 58 min, CCTV labeled "U140", cuid2301 (Box 157)
  - Video 1038: My Memories of Old Beijing, 47 mins, CCTV labeled "U141", cuid2302 (Box 157)
  - Video 1039: The New Puritans: the Sikhs of Yuba City, Produced by Ritu Sarin and Tenzing Sonam, 24 mins 18 sec, CCTV labeled "U186", cuid2303 (Box 158)
  - Video 1040: Nok Lare (40:00 min) and Don't Follow Me/Don't Talk to Me by Teeraneetee Tamrongweenijchai, CCTV labeled "U208", cuid2304 (Box 158)
  - Video 1041: Pearls #6: Fujikawa by Michael Toshiyuki Uno, 30 mins, CCTV labeled "U168/U178", cuid2305 (Box 158)
  - Video 1042: 1984 Video Festival films: "Perceptions: A Question of Justice" by Sandra Gin Yep (25 min); "Perceptions: Japanese American Redress" by Sandra Gin Yep (25 min), CCTV labeled "U146", cuid2306 (Box 158)
  - Video 1043: 1984 Video Festival film "Perceptions: Japanese American Redress" by Sandra Gin Yep (25 min), CCTV labeled "U146", cuid2307 (Box 158)
  - Video 1044: Philippine Cinema London Video (also called Film in the Philippines) by Ron Orders, Large Door Unlimited, 37 mins, CCTV labeled "U184", cuid2308 (Box 158)
  - Video 1045: Shradanjali, CCTV labeled "U142", cuid2309 (Box 158)
  - Video 1046: Tibet (Documentary), Producer/Director: Nien-Sheng Lin, Ph.D., 49 mins, CCTV labeled "U137", cuid2310 (Box 158)
  - Video 1047: Yuki Shimoda: Asian American Actor by Amy Kato and John Esako, 30 mins, CCTV labeled "U211", cuid2311 (Box 158)
  - Video 1048: 1984 Video Festival films: "As the Wheels Turn" by Fredric Mao (11 mins 30 sec); "Video Installations by Shigeko Kubato (12 mins); "Japan Love, Honto" by Ann Eugenia Volkes (12 mins); "Reaching for the Stars" by Nancy Tong (24 mins), CCTV lab, cuid2312 (Box 159)
  - Video 1049: Asian Women Video Artists: "Birds" by Rii Kanazaki (8 mins), "Brighton" by Rii Kanazaki (3 mins 30 sec), "Hawaii" by Rii Kanazaki (15 mins 30 sec), "Manong" by Linda Mabalot (30 mins), CCTV labeled "U151", cuid2313 (Box 159)
  - Video 1050: Dollar a day, 10 cents a dance produced by George Ow Jr. (28.40 min), CCTV labeled "U159", cuid2314 (Box 159)
  - Video 1051: 1984 AAIFF film: East to West by Yaping Wang, 60 mins, CCTV labeled "U156/U166", cuid2315 (Box 159)
  - Video 1052: 1984 AAIFF film: First Look by Kavery Dutta, 60 mins, CCTV labeled "U155", cuid2316 (Box 159)
  - Video 1053: Kind of Yellow by David Chan (20 min) and Community Plot by JT Takaji (20 min), CCTV labeled "U157/U167", cuid2317 (Box 159)
  - Video 1054: Pacific Bridges: To a New Land by Noel Izon, 30 mins, CCTV labeled "U169/U179", cuid2318 (Box 159)
  - Video 1055: Pearls #1: Emi by Michael Toshiyuki Uno, 28 mins, CCTV labeled "U165/U175", cuid2319 (Box 159)
  - Video 1056: Pearls #2: Mako by Frank Nesbitt, 29 mins, CCTV labeled "U166/U176", cuid2320 (Box 159)
  - Video 1057: Broken Diary: Ch. 11, cuid2321 (Box 160)
  - Video 1058: The Open Window (Music by Jason Hwang), cuid2322 (Box 160)
  - Video 1059: Senjyu Can Non Kyu Seigen 1986 AAIVF (5:17), cuid2323 (Box 160)
  - Video 1060: The Shining Hour (1986 AAIVF) Morifumi Arimura, cuid2324 (Box 160)
  - Video 1061: Tomiyo Sasaki, cuid2325 (Box 160)
  - Video 1062: They Speak of Hope by Fern Lee Hagedon, cuid2326 (Box 160)
  - Video 1063: Tsumiki + Building Blocks 2 by Hiromu Saiki, cuid2327 (Box 160)
  - Video 1064: Two Comedians: Phil Nee + Stan Egi at the Middle of the Road, cuid2328 (Box 160)
  - Video 1065: Winter Chill Malcolm S. Wong, cuid2329 (Box 160)
  - Video 1066: Year of the Rat by Sasha Lee, cuid2330 (Box 160)
  - Video 1067: Arnie Wong Tigerly Inc., cuid2331 (Box 161)
  - Video 1068: Cheung on Chi, cuid2332 (Box 161)
  - Video 1069: Fear of Failure Malcolm S. Wong Tape 1, cuid2333 (Box 161)
  - Video 1070: Grass or When the Rain Falls - Janice Tanaka 1986 AAIVF (5:30), New York Hot Springs Taka Iimura 1986 AAIVF (11:00), cuid2334 (Box 161)
  - Video 1071: Hard Contact Hiroya Sakurai 1986 AAIVF, cuid2335 (Box 161)
  - Video 1072: India Cabaret by Mira Nair 11/15/85, cuid2336 (Box 161)
  - Video 1073: Naked Spaces Tape 1, cuid2337 (Box 161)
  - Video 1074: Naked Spaces Tape 2, cuid2338 (Box 161)
  - Video 1075: Naked Spaces Tape 3, cuid2339 (Box 161)
  - Video 1076: 1987 AAIFF Trailer Dub and Titles, cuid2340 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1076)
    Duration: 2 minutes
  - Video 1077: Do Si Te by Alan Nakagawa, cuid2341 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1077, Box Shared Tamiment 157, Folder 1)
  - Video 1078: Flight of Ideas by Fu-Ding Chen, cuid2343 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1078)
    Duration: 15 minutes
  - Video 1079: The Long Weekend by Gregg Araki, cuid2344 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1079)
  - Video 1080: The Long Weekend by Gregg Araki, cuid2345 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1080)
    Duration: 33 minutes
  - Video 1081: Orientations by Richard Fung, 4th AAIVF, cuid2346 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1081)
    Duration: 56 minutes
  - Video 1082: Paris by Ping Chong / Meredith Mok, 4th AAIVF, cuid2347 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1082)
    Duration: 30 minutes
  - Video 1083: Spalding Gray's Map of L.A. by Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, 4th AAIVF, cuid2348 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1083)
    Duration: 28 minutes
  - Video 1084: 10th annual Nihonmachi Street Fair by S. Nakasako, cuid2349 (Box 162, U-matic Video 1084)
    Duration: 25 minutes
  - Video 1085: Asian Studs Nightmare, cuid2350 (Box 163)
  - Video 1086: "Camp Arirang" by Diana S. Lee and Grace Yoon-Kyung Lee, cuid2351 (Box 163)
  - Video 1087: Dirty Laundry by Richard Fung, cuid2352 (Box 163)
  - Video 1088: Fingers and Kisses, Coming Home by Shu Lea Cheang, cuid2353 (Box 163)
  - Video 1089:Fingers and Kisses, Coming Home by Shu Lea Cheang, cuid2354 (Box 163)
  - Video 1090: Footsteps, cuid2355 (Box 163)
  - Video 1091: L.A. Christmas by Kip Fulbeck, cuid2356 (Box 163)
  - Video 1092: Leaving Bakul Bagan, cuid2357 (Box 163)
  - Video 1093: A Letter from Home (a work in progress), cuid2358 (Box 163)
  - Video 1094: Merits of Life, cuid2359 (Box 164)
  - Video 1095: "Then", cuid2360 (Box 164)
  - Video 1096: Videos by Kimberly Saree Tomes, cuid2361 (Box 164)
  - Video 1097: "Singapore Report: Industrial Revolution", cuid2362 (Box 164)
  - Video 1098: Stopover by Larry Hoki, cuid2363 (Box 164)
  - Video 1099: Sweet Jail: The Sikhs of Yuba City by Beheroze F. Shroff, cuid2364 (Box 164)
  - Video 1100: Tongpan by Surachay Jantimathorn, cuid2365 (Box 164)
  - Video 1101: AKA Don Bonus, cuid2366 (Box 164)
  - Video 1102: Off Limits by Rea Tajiri, cuid2367 (Box 164)
  - Video 1103: "Out in the Open" by Renu Lobo, cuid2368 (Box 164)
  - Video 1104: Bittersweet Survival by Christine Choy / J.T. Takagi (27 min), cuid2369 (Box 165)
  - Video 1105: Coming to America by Renu Lobo, cuid2370 (Box 165)
  - Video 1106: Poppo at E'Village 4 (Oct 24), cuid2371 (Box 165)